Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority metrorail specifications records, 1962-1980 MS2021
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Specifications, 1956-1974; MS2021 Series 3; 4.5 Linear feet
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Invitation for Bid, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Pre-Award Evaluation Data, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Bid Form for Construction Contract, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Index, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Table of Contents, Section 2%32882015254892, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, General Provisions, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, Section 2, Special Provisions, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.2, Support, Alteration, and Restoration of Structures, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.3, Excavation and Backfill, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.4, Temporary and Permanent Groundwater Control, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.5, Support of Excavation, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.6, Maintenance, Support, Relocation, and Restoration of Utilities, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.7, Decking of Streets, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.8, Portland Cement Concrete, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.9, Reinforcing Steel, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.10, Concrete Structures, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.11, Prestressed Concrete, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.12, Structural Steel, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.13, Miscellaneous Iron and Steel, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.14, Subway Drainage, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.15, Sewage and Drainage, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.16, Water Mains, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.17, Electrical Work, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.18, Mechanical Work, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.19, Portland Cement Concrete Pavement, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.20, Bituminous Pavements, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.21, Waterproofing, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.23, Base for Pavements, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.24, Curbs, Gutters, Sidewalks, and Medians, 1970 June (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.26, Foundation Caissons, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.28, Bearing Pads, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.44, Corrosion Control, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 3.47, Precast Concrete, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 5.4, Sprayed-on Fireproofing, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-3, Connecticut Avenue, 1A0031, 5.7, Masonry, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-4a, Connecticut Avenue Route, 1969 December (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-4b, Connecticut Avenue Route, 1970 December (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-6a, Rockville Route, Rock Tunnels, 1A0061, 1972 September (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Sections B009, B010, and B011, Glenmont B Route, Engineering Analysis, 1977 October (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Sections B009, B010, and B011, Glenmont B Route, Engineering Analysis, 1977 October (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6e, Glenmont Route, Silver Spring Station Site, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6e, Glenmont Route, Silver Spring Station Site, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6e, Glenmont Route, Silver Spring Station Site, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6e, Glenmont Route, Silver Spring Station Site, 1976 November (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section D-7, New Carrollton Route, Potomac Avenue Station, 1D0071, 1972 July (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section D-7, New Carrollton Route, Potomac Avenue Station, 1D0071, 1972 July (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section D-7, New Carrollton Route, Potomac Avenue Station, 1D0071, 1972 July (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section E002, Greenbelt Route, Comparative Cost Studies, 1974 September (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section E002, Design Concepts for Greenbelt Route, 1974 September (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section E002, Underpinning Report, Volume I, 1974 August (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section F003, Branch Route, Design Contract, 1973 April (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section FA-3, Rockville Route, Farragut North Station, 1A3031, 1972 November (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section FA-3, Rockville Route, Farragut North Station, 1A3031, 1972 November (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section FA-3, Rockville Route, Farragut North Station, 1A3031, 1972 November (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Air Conditioning for Passenger Stations, 1968 June (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Automatic Train Control Project, Contract Modification Documents, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Contract Specifications, Rapid Transit Cars, 2Z0065, 1978 November (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: General Railway Signal Company, Contract 1Z2011, Changes, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Invitation for Bid, Control and Communications, 1Z2011, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Invitation for Bid, Control and Communications, 1Z2011, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Invitation for Bid, Control and Communications, 1Z2011, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Office of Construction, Construction Program, 1970 February (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Request for Technical Proposal, Rapid Transit Cars, 2Z8061, 1971 January (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-3a, WTC Steam and Air Facilities, 1B0031, 1971 September (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5a, Major Repair Shop Transit Car Hoist Equipment, 1Z420A, 1971 September (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5a, Major Repair Shop Transit Car Hoist Equipment, 1Z420A, 1971 September (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5a, Major Repair Shop Transit Car Hoist Equipment, 1Z420A, 1971 September (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5c3, WTC Alterations, 1970 October (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5d, Model of Electrical System, 1970 May (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section B-5d2, Glenmont Route, Model of Electrical System, 1970 June (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Section E002, Groundwater Control Report to Board of Engineering Consultants, 1975 July (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Stage SSE-1, Substation Equipment, Phase I, 2Z1031, 1971 January (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Oversize documents, 1959-1980; MS2021 Series 4; 9 Linear feet
  This series contains bound reports and specifications that needed oversize boxes for archival storage and covers the dates 1959-80. The material is arranged with groupings for series one through three with an additional section in the series Specifications to accommodate documents generated by agencies other than NCTA or WMATA. All reports and specification documents are arranged alphabetically. The blueprints including map-size folders related to track switching procedures are arranged in numerical order by drawing number and then by further identifying number.
  The reports section includes documents for the budget and finances and other miscellaneous topics that outline fiscal plans, feasibility studies, and environmental impact studies. The Specifications section of oversize documents is divided into the following subjects; bridges, highways, and roads, miscellaneous, and rail rapid transit. The rail rapid transit section is further divided into route designs and support equipment as well as specification documents produced by other transit agencies including Metropolitan Atlanta Region Transit Authority and Southeast Michigan Transit Authority.
  - Reports, Budget and Finances: Preliminary Design and Capital Costs, Adopted Regional System, 1969 February (Oversize 20, Folder 1)
  - Reports, Budget and Finances: Report on Design Studies and Cost Estimates, Penn Central Railroad Bridge, 1971 January (Oversize 20, Folder 2)
  - Reports, Budget and Finances: Summary of Capital Costs, Proposed Regional System, Originals, 1969 February (Oversize 20, Folder 3)
  - Reports, Budget and Finances: Supplemental Report on Design Studies and Cost Estimates, Penn Central Railroad Bridge, 1971 January (Oversize 20, Folder 4)
  - Reports, Budget and Finances: Traffic, Revenue, and Operating Costs, Adopted Regional System, 1969 February (Oversize 20, Folder 5)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous: Environmental Impact Statement and Study of Routes C, D, and L, 1973 May (Oversize 20, Folder 6)
  - Reports, Miscellaneous: Mass Transportation Survey, National Capital Region, Civil Engineering Report, 1959 January (Oversize 20, Folder 7)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: Completing the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways in the District of Columbia, 1960 August 01 (Oversize 21, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: 11th Street Bridge, SW, Connection to 12th Street Expressway, Federal-Aid Project S-SG-72(1), 1960 (Oversize 21, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: Feasibility Study, MacArthur Boulevard, 1967 June (Oversize 21, Folder 3)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: Location Studies, Interstate Route 266, 1964 September (Oversize 21, Folder 4)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: 9th Street Expressway, Contract Number 4, Federal Aid Project US 225(6), 1967 March (Oversize 21, Folder 5)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: Railroad Bridge over New York Avenue, NE, Federal-Aid Project U-UG-106(9), 1967 May (Oversize 21, Folder 6)
  - Specifications; Bridges, Highways, and Roads: Superstructure for New West Highway Bridge over Potomac River, Vicinity of 14th Street, Federal-Aid Interstate Project Number I-95-1(24)0, Contract 2S, 1959 (Oversize 21, Folder 7)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Design and Construction Schedule, 1972 November (Oversize 21, Folder 8)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Miscellaneous Originals, 1967-1968 (Oversize 21, Folder 9)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: NPS Permanent Stable, 1A0047, 1971 July (Oversize 21, Folder 10)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Park Police Stables, Section A-4a, 1A0045, 1970 February (Oversize 21, Folder 11)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, Airlie II System, Originals, 1967 December (Oversize 21, Folder 12)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, Airlie IIA, System, Originals, 1967 December (Oversize 21, Folder 13)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, Blank Form, Originals, undated (Oversize 21, Folder 14)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, System "A", Originals, 1967 December (Oversize 22, Folder 1)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, System "B", Originals, 1967 December (Oversize 22, Folder 2)
  - Specifications, Miscellaneous: Summary of Capital Costs, System "C", Originals, 1967 December (Oversize 22, Folder 3)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Directive Drawings, 1970-1975 (Oversize 22, Folder 4)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Directive Drawings, 1970-1975 (Oversize 22, Folder 5)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Directive Drawings, 1970-1975 (Oversize 23, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Drawings to Accompany Engineering Feasibility and Development Studies of Rapid Transit Systems and Equipment for the National Capital region, Volume III, 1963 (Oversize 23, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Drawings TSCI-TC-007 to TSCI-TC-119, untitled volume, 1970 (Oversize 23, Folder 3)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Index of Civil, TW, R/W Directive Drawings, 1980 February (Oversize 23, Folder 4)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A009, Structural Contract A9b, 1975 (Oversize 24, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-2, Connecticut Avenue Route, 1A0021, 1969 October (Oversize 25, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-4a, Connecticut Avenue Route, 1A0043, 1969 December (Oversize 25, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A-6a, Rockville Route, 1A0061, 1972 September (Oversize 26, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A6b, Rockville Route, 1A0062, 1975 December (Oversize 27, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section A11a, Rockville Route, 1A0111, 1975 February (Oversize 28, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-2, B&O Route, 1B0021, 1970 June (Oversize 29, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-4, B&O Route, 1B0043, 1970 February (Oversize 29, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6, Glenmont Route, 1B0063, 1972 December (Oversize 29, Folder 3)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section B-6, Glenmont Route, 1B0063, 1972 December (Oversize 30, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section D-1, Huntington and New Carrollton Route, Federal Triangle Station, 1D0011, 1972 May (Oversize 31, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section D-3, Ardmore Route, 1D0031, 1972 February (Oversize 31, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section F-004, Branch Route, 1F0041, 1980 June (Oversize 32, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section FA-1, Connecticut Avenue Route, 1A3011, 1972 November (Oversize 32, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section FC-5, Huntington Route, 1C3051, 1974 July (Oversize 32, Folder 3)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section G-2, Addison Route, 1G0021, 1975 November (Oversize 33, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Section L-1, L'Enfant Plaza-Pentagon Route, 1L0011, 1975 November (Oversize 33, Folder 2)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: "Standard Drawings", 1968-1973 (Oversize 34, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Trackwork-6, Information of Drawings, 1Z4086, 1980 January (Oversize 35, Folder 1)
  - Specifications; Rail Rapid Transit, Route Designs: Underpinning Report, Greenbelt Route, Section E-002, 1974 August (Oversize 35, Folder 2)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Elevators I, 1Z4141, 1973 November (Oversize 35, Folder 3)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Escalators IV, 1Z4054, 1976 October (Oversize 35, Folder 4)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Escalators VII, 1Z4057, 1979 August (Oversize 35, Folder 5)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Fire Protection Lines, Phase 2, 1Z019B, 1975 December (Oversize 35, Folder 6)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Fire Protection Lines, Phase 2A, 1Z029A, 1975 November (Oversize 35, Folder 7)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Drawings, Fire Protection Lines, Phase 2C, 1Z019C, 1975 October (Oversize 36, Folder 1)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Emergency Communications, 1Z202H, 1979 November (Oversize 36, Folder 2)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Graphics, Stage 1, 1Z0091, 1974 February (Oversize 36, Folder 3)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Kiosks I, 1Z3091, 1974 May (Oversize 36, Folder 4)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Kiosks III, 1Z3093, 1976 October (Oversize 36, Folder 5)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Request for Technical Proposal, Rapid Transit Cars, 2Z8061, 1971 January (Oversize 36, Folder 6)
  - Specifications, Rail Rapid Transit, Support Equipment: Stage SSE-1, Substation Equipment, Phase I, 2Z1031, 1970 June (Oversize 36, Folder 7)
  - Specifications, Specifications by Other Transit Agencies: East Line Construction, Arizona Avenue Underpass, Contract CF-191, Metropolitan Atlanta Rapid Transit Authority, 1974 (Oversize 37, Folder 1)
  - Specifications, Specifications by Other Transit Agencies: Preliminary Engineering Report, New Tran Detroit CBD People Mover, undated (Oversize 37, Folder 2)
  - Southeast Michigan Transit Authority, 1975 June (Oversize 37, Folder 3)
  - Specifications, Specifications by Other Transit Agencies: South Shore Marina, Inner Harbor Project, 1977 January (Oversize 37, Folder 4)
  - Specifications, Specifications by Other Transit Agencies: Stamford Station, Northeast Corridor Improvement Project, 1980 July (Oversize 37, Folder 5)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-217-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-217-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-217-1, 1973 April (Oversize 38, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-218, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-218, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 5)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71908, A-218-1, 1973 April (Oversize 38, Folder 6)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-219-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 7)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-220-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 8)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-221-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 9)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-222-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 10)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-223-0, 1973 May (Oversize 38, Folder 11)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-224-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-225-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-226-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-227-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-228-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 5)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71910, A-229-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 6)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71910, A-230-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 7)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-231-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 8)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing 91-71907, A-232-0, 1973 May (Oversize 39, Folder 9)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing A03-G-15, A-217-2, 1973 October (Oversize 39, Folder 10)
  - Blueprint Drawings: Drawing A03-G-16, A-218-2, 1973 October (Oversize 39, Folder 11)